[{"answer": "Why can't I play my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Neither are you", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Oh come on my friend. How hard is it to act. You say something, I'll pretend it's funny", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Ha ha ha. Your grandmother's in the hospital", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Well, really, it's very unusual. It's about nothing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " For example, what did you do today", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Yes. Yes, it's white. Why it's white", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Yes. Yes, it's white. Why it's white", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Better get that checked out", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What are you like a sadist? No matter how bad somebody feels, you can make 'em feel worse. I bet you're rooting for a tumor.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Oh I'm going baby! I'm going!  ", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh, my God", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " It's all white my friend! It's all white", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Again with the checked out. I'm not going to the doctor. If I don't to the doctor, then nothing will happen to me. If I go he might find something", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Catch what in time", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You're in latex", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't know, you manufacture it. ", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well, h", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "He was you know... he was touching and rubbing.", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "O.K", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What look", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What look", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I gave a look", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What is this about", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Levels", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yeah. I'm getting rid of all, all my furniture. All of it! I'm building... levels... with steps... completely carpeted...  with pillows.  Like Ancient that place", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Oh! I'll be comfortable.", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You see, It's right here. It's all white..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You've never seen this before", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I'm gonna have to take a biopsy on that.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "A biopsy", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " A what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "A biopsy", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Well I don't know what it is. ", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "A biopsy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "He said he didn't know what it was", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Alright. So", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Well, maybe he doesn't have a", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " Have you seen the waitresses in there lately? I never had so much coffee in my life", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Apply for a job? What for", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "You gotta play him like me. I'm my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pilot-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Whoa, I'm my friend.", "qsentId": 44}]